♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we've got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we'll reset it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko stronger after all ♪
A horrible tragedy may explain the rumor that there’s a ghost somewhere at the Kadic Academy.
Back in 1905 while the building was under construction...
One of the workers, Leon Corbe is said to have been buried alive under the foundations.
In the boiler room area to be precise.
Not even believeable.
Get real.
Emily 77, good work.
Gene 87, very good.
Elizabeth, a quadrilateral is not a quadrant-you-do-later.
Ten.
Jeremy, I deducted two points for the ketchup stain on your diagram, 98.
Ulrich, there’s some good,
but not enough to make up for what’s bad. 58.
Herb 93, excellent!
Not as good as Jeremy, but excellent nevertheless.
Odd--
Meet me in the boiler room at midnight, Sissi?
May I remind you that in the evening, girls and boys are prohibited from straying from their respective floors.
Okay.
For any of you who might be thinking
of trying to pull anything--
--Remember that the floors are different from each other
in that they're either upstairs from--
--or downstairs from the one above.
Girls are upstairs and boys downstairs.
Comings and goings from upstairs to downstairs and
from downstairs to upstairs are strictly forbidden.
And if I ever catch anyone going
from downstairs upstairs--
--or anyone going from upstairs to downstairs,
he or she is really going to regret it stairs.
You’ve been warned.
Dismissed.
Password?
Uh, you didn’t give me one.
Correct! Come in.
Isn’t this a bit square for you?
It’s not a square, it’s a tempogram.
Pentagram.
Whatever.
Thanks to this and my psychic powers,
I’m going to conjure the spirit of that poor Leon Corbe.
I’m sure if we communicate with him,
he can finally rest in peace.
I can’t wait to see this.
Okay, now stand inside the pentagon with me.
We will bring together our ping and pong energy.
And summon up the dead man’s ghost.
You know what?
I think you forgot the paddles.
And now, let the ceremony begin.
De profundis tenebrae (x8)
I summon you Leon Corbe!
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Yes Leon, I’m listening.
Don’t step out of the pentacolon Ulrich, it protects us.
Uh, Leon Corbe?
Darnit, he’s gone!
He doesn’t wanna speak to me.
Behind you!
(SCREAMS)
Let’s go, quick!
Come on!
It was horrible Jim, really. I swear it’s true!
Come on you two, calm down.
The ghost of Leon Corbe came after us in the boiler room Jim!
If anyone’s after you two,
it’s a gym teacher in a tracksuit,--
--holding a red pen,
which he’s gonna use to give you four hours of detention.
We better go upstairs fast.
Sissi, you better go back to your room.
No. Don’t leave me all by myself, please?
Shh… Alright, come in then.
Wait for me here, I’ll be back.
Am I dreaming or what?
I’m scared Odd, mind if I sit near you?
Uh-huh, it’s just a nightmare and soon I’m gonna wake up.
Jeremie. I think XANA has just launched an attack.
Uh, the laptop.
We’ll know in a minute.
Nope, there are no activated towers.
It looks like we’ve got a real ghost on our hands then.
A what?
Someone around here is gonna be in real trouble!
So, Leon’s ghost came out of the boiler and--
And he was so ugly that even--
--Nicholas and Herb started screaming!
(SCREAMING)
Jim!
You okay Jim?
Yeah, yeah I’m alright.
What’s that noise?
I don’t know, but it’s getting closer.
You saw right, the monster did pixelize when I hit it.
It’s gotta be one of XANA’s.
So why didn’t the superscan pick it up then?
I wish I knew, we better head for the Factory.
Let’s get Aelita.
(SCREAMING)
(CELLPHONE RINGING)
Hello?
It’s me, there’s a big emergency,
meet us at the Factory.
Got it.
Jeremie?
Aelita.
Jeremie!
Hey, this is no time to hang around.
Hurry, it’s coming!
What took you so long?
XANA’s attacking us,
but the superscan didn’t detect anything.
Do you believe in ghosts?
No?
Wrong answer.
Hey! That’s weird…
XANA’s managed to corrupt the superscan.
There’s an activated tower,
but it can’t detect it.
Right. So what do we do now?
Yumi and Aelita, get to Sector Five as quickly--
--as you can and try to fix the superscan.
Odd and Ulrich in the meantime,
you can check out the other sectors.
With a little luck,
you’ll be able to spot the activated tower.
Negative, the spectre will strike back soon,
I’m staying with you.
Well okay.
I’ll launch the process.
Transfer, Aelita.
Transfer, Yumi.
Transfer, Odd.
Virtualization!
Nice to see you without your pajamas on.
Nice of you to notice.
Jeremie, I’m gonna need a--
Okay, forget it.
Later!
Can you bring up the transporter Jeremie?
It’s on the way.
The countdown has started.
Remember, you only have three minutes to find the key.
Jeremie.
What do we do?
Come on.
The Desert looks normal.
I’ll move on to another sector.
Can’t shake him!
There’s no point running,
he’ll catch us every time.
You got a better idea?
I see the key.
Too good to be true.
Look out!
(SCREAMING)
Yumi!
Jeremie?
How much time do we have left?
Jeremie? Jeremie!
This is getting creepy.
Great. That’s all we needed.
Darn it, still no activated tower.
I must be jinxed.
Wait, I have an idea.
Alright, I get it.
Shouldn’t something be happening here?
No!
Concentrate, there’s still time to get out of here.
Ulrich, I wouldn’t mind a little help right now!
Where there’s smoke…
Come on Yumi, you can make it!
No!
Yumi!
Jeremie we didn’t get the key,
I’m all alone.
Man… He was a tough one.
Let’s get to the Factory,
the others probably need us.
Jeremie, I’ve found the tower!
Jeremie?
Uh oh.
Jeremie, what’s going on?
Don’t panic, I’ll get you outta there.
(SCREAMING)
Jeremie! I don’t like the looks of this!
Yumi!
Aelita’s all alone in the Arena.
Hurry up.
Jeremie…
Jeremie!
Jeremie? Ulrich?
Help me!
Oh man… How does this thing work?
Well, Fritz Uncleberd has done it again,
his third straight title. What a champ! He’s amazing.
Wow, he even has TV on his computer.
Jeremie!
No, it’s not Jeremie. It’s Odd.
Odd, type in the code. SCIPIO.
Quick!
Uh, I’d love to but how?
Third window on the second screen.
Okay, I got it. S-C-I-P-I-O
There.
Aelita, I spotted the activated tower--
--in the north-west part of the Ice sector.
Okay, I’ll go. But where’s Jeremie?
And Ulrich?
No idea. I’ll go look for them.
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
(SCREAMING)
Well… Not feeling so cocky, are we?
(HUMMING CONTINUES)
Tower deactivated.
You okay guys?
Say something.
Something.
Hey, no stealing my jokes. Okay?
Since we didn’t fix the superscan in Sector Five,
we have no choice.
We’ve gotta launch a return in time.
Return to the past, now.
And now, let the ceremony begin.
De profundis tenebrae (x8)
I summon you Leon Corbe!
Who dares call my name?
Well, I do.
Beat it Ms. Delmas.
You don’t know who you’re dealing with.
Scram!
(SCREAMING)
You can come out now.
Well…
I don’t think she’s gonna try--
--to wake the dead again.
(LAUGHTER)
(GHOSTLY WIND)
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY THE FOXTROT FANATICS